Mutual fund investments are subject to
market risks. Read all scheme related
documents carefully.
Hello, welcome to Amar Ujala The Bonus.
I am your friend
Harsh Sharma and if you look at yesterday's markets,
what a great rally there was.  Where the opening
remained almost in the same range, it means that the trader did
not have many options
here, but yes, it definitely happened that the market has
succeeded in making a good rise here.  What are the next triggers for the market now
?  Because we give
you war updates every day.
Because nowadays the
market moves according to the news.
There is a rise or fall.  So first of all let's
start from there here.  So you
see what are the major updates in the US and Iran war,
here after the market closed yesterday,
you see the first big
news that came out was that brother, there is a consideration to extend the ceasefire by two weeks.
How far is the ceasefire now?  It is here till 22nd.
But now such news has come out
quoting AP and Bloomberg
that this ceasefire can be
considered to be extended by two weeks.  But
immediately after this, a statement
came from America that there is no news regarding extension of ceasefire.
These are false news.
But the news market is very sad.
And that's why we felt we should
share this with you.  What is the third thing that
happened here?  Look, a threat came from Iran.
Iran clearly said that
they can close the three sea routes
here.  I will tell you why you can close it,
but they clearly say
that the blockade that America has imposed on Hormus is
clearly a
violation of the ceasefire and that is why we will
close the Red Sea, Oman Sea and Persian Gulf,
trade there will be completely
stopped, so this
threat is also being given, along with this you can
see that talks were being held between Israel and Lebanon, as far as
I remember,
in 1993 they were sitting at the table and
discussions were held together and after that, now
after so many years, the discussions between Israel and Lebanon are being
seen taking place.  Now we
will tell you whatever conclusion we reach here.  But it is
certain that now the talks, whether it is
between America and Israel, Iran, or
between Israel and Lebanon, that discussion is
seen taking place here.  Now
we will see whether the ceasefire is extended by two weeks
or not.  But now
if you look at what are the big challenges for the market, then first of all let
me tell you about crude here
because on the basis of crude the market used to
move forward and decrease.  Here crude
is currently trading around $95 per barrel if we talk about brand crude.  So, that
means there is no
major crisis here at the moment.  It has
not gone above 100 here.  The second thing
here, according to our markets, you should understand
that today is the expiry of Sussex.  The
market has broken the four-day range.  There was
an important range
which had to be broken.  Now you understand here
that the 50 day average of Nifty here
in 50 days is the
level of 24446.  This level is a very crucial
level.  He will cross it or not
because it requires strength.   It will be
important to understand here what kind of strength will come in the market and from where will this strength come, sector wise or in terms of the purchases made by FIC.  But the resistance level is clearly from
24,350 to 24,450 and the support
level is 24,000 and 23,900, that is,
this support level here is not
only better from the psychological point of view but
also the position of put writers
is much better here.  Depending on the results of Quarter 4 and the movement of monsoon, the
strength in the market will be seen here.  If the
results continue to be good, the market may see an increase.  Such
possibilities are visible.  And the dollar index is
trading below 100
here.  So this is a good thing.
Came down to a level of around 98.  Could be a positive market-
wise.  But there's
another big thing here.  Look, trade
deficit has come out here.  The FI of 2526 has
increased from $94.6 billion
to $119 billion.  That means the deficit
seems to be increasing significantly.  This will be a
matter of concern here and this becomes
very important from the economic point of view.
These were the triggers here.
Now which specific stocks do you have to keep an
eye on because today is a
big day of results, there are many.  Results of about 14 companies will be seen coming.  We will remain with
Wipro.
Also look at the buyback, there are full
news regarding Wipro.  Now
what will be the results of Wipro after TCS?  We will
tell you this and make you understand this thing.  Jal
Forest results will be seen coming.  Forests are
renewables.  AOK Industries Reliance
has a stake in it.  rzbles
finance SG Fans, Ganesh Holding and Amir
Chand Jagdish which have been listed recently
and after the listing, for the first time the
company will be seen presenting its results
here and apart from this there are many other
companies too, their results will be seen coming, that
means there are 14 companies whose results will come,
you should keep a close eye on this, let us tell
you what GIFT Nifty is indicating, a
rise of approximately 77 points, that
means there may be some more strength which
GIFT Nifty
is indicating.  What is happening in the market can give the possibility of a rise.  The one
around 1/4 is
showing an increase for now.  Let us present
before you what has been the stance of FI and DI.
Look, in the last few times, I have been
saying this again and again that DIs are
repeatedly selling
or their number of
purchases is decreasing in comparison to FIs.
But now, FI had made purchases two-three days ago also.
Now this is what the FI has done
once again, making a purchase of around Rs 667 crore.
So, the net that has come out to you is approximately Rs
97 crore.  If you
go by the index, then FI has made purchases in the index,
Nifty and Bank Nifty.
You can look at index
futures, which I keep talking about.
Look, here in the index future you can
clearly see it in green.
Purchases worth more than Rs 1200 crore have been made.
Sold in index options.  The stock has been
sold in futures.  It is clearly visible.
But net shorts have also capitalized.
Put shorts are also capitalized here.  So
you must keep these things in
mind.  Further, if we
talk about strike prices here, then see,
if you talk about calls in the strike price, first of all,
where are the put writers
and where are the call writers sitting, then at the top,
almost above 24200,
you will see that the positioning of call writers is very strong,
here the OI is the highest,
after that the next number is 24500, but right
now 24200, which is the crucial level, is
visible, if we
talk about the positions of putters, here
I deliberately brought 24200, you will see that the
fight is tough.  So will the
market be seen in a state of consolidation
?  We will see this in the markets today and
understand it here.  But apart from this, it becomes even
more important for you to understand what is the trend and environment in the global market.
So you
see, yesterday was a great day in the global market.   In
a way, understand that a tremendous rise was seen in the American market.
You can understand this in Wall Street, whether you look at SNP 500
or NSDDC, they have hit a new high.  A
record high was set here.  Even if we
look at Dubjosons futures, there is a
rise of approximately 0.19% here.  The
reason behind this rise has been the
strong results of Morgan Stanley.   There is a
jump of 5%.  Apart from this, Bank of
America has shown record trading revenue
here.  So this business
trading business has seen a good growth.  There has been
a good growth in commodity trading here, the
effect of which is
visible in the markets here.  And there are
many such companies, one
shoe company flopped badly but
it said no to AI and said that we will start our business
according to AI.  Will we
invest here in a new way and
what has the stock run up?  What a great rally it was.
So all those things but if we
talk about Asian markets, Asian markets are also
seen trading on a positive note.
So, overall, I have presented before you the equations of
global markets across the world and our markets.
Now let us add Rajesh Bansal
ji.
Thank you very much Rajesh Sir.  Good morning for joining us.
Greeting sir.
Greeting sir.  Rai Sir, the rise that happened yesterday was because we went to the
indication of Gift Nifty and remained
in the same position the whole day.
We did not see any very low
position. What
indication is being given by these things Sir,
no. After the gap up opening yesterday, the
market sustained the whole day, this is a very positive
indication
and it consolidated by staying in a range, so for the
first time the market is showing that if the gap
down opens then it covers up and comes up
and if the gap up opens then it stands cheap.  The
market showed a huge positivity
yesterday that it was able to sustain after such a huge gap up
and remember the last time
when the market came up again and again, it got rejected from 24300 and
went down and during that time
a gap was formed
between 24415 and 303, so the market
will try to fill that gap today and
closing above 24415 will be another positive
aspect, let us see whether it comes or
not, today, tomorrow or the day after tomorrow, the
market is showing strength.  Sustaining it.  He has come
up after fighting so much from the lower levels.  Gap up is
covering gap down.  Sustaining the gap up above.  There
is very good positivity for the market.
Sir, which levels did you tell me below which it should
close, so that we can believe that there is more strength
here.
24415 was a gap and closing above it
means a lot of positivity in the market.  Ok
?  And here also we were telling our viewers
that the level of 24,446 is
around 50 DMA.  Now we will see.  Well, as Sir
told, levels are very
important here.  So what should be the strategy for today,
sir?  What are the levels where one should
adopt a buy or buy dips strategy?   If
someone is an intraday trader today, then
as soon as the market opens, it fluctuates.  That
is a trade just for opening.
If Nifi gets spot from 24,330 to 340 then one can short there.
Intraday the market can come down to 24,250 or 220.
And those who do not want to do short should
leave it for small trades and
buy from 24,210 to 250.   Place
stop loss below 24,130.  The target
will be 24360
minimum
ideally and the market can also go up to 24410.
Okay sir, so the possibility of 24410 means
you are seeing possibilities around 24400 in today's market.  Yes, today the
market should go up to 24400 and if by mistake it
reaches 24410440 then it can also short there, by
placing stop loss above 24450,
50-60 points can be gained intraday, so today one
can trade there at two or three places, if someone
is a trader, an intraday trader, then he will get two or three
opportunities and the actual trade that he wants to do is
wait for it to come down,
buy and exit after taking his profit,
okay sir, so thank you very much sir, you have
explained a very good strategy to our viewers, I think if they follow it then it is
possible that we may see
positive results in the future.  Thank you so much
sir.  Thank you so much sir.
Greeting sir.
So overall this was Rajesh Bansal ji whose
strategy we share with you daily.
Now let us tell you where important levels should be paid
attention to.  Now we welcome VL Ambala
Ma'am.
Thank you very much ma'am for giving us your valuable time.
Thank you so much Harsh.  Good morning to all
viewers.  Thank you.   Yes.
And meanwhile, many of our viewers
like Sampat Sharma ji are saying Jai Shri Ram
and many more are saying Good Morning.
So a very good morning to everyone.
Good luck to you, may this day be full of fun.
Cut very well.  Ambala Ma'am, I
want to understand from you.  Now tell me one thing about the market,
first of all I will tell you because we
understand things one by one.
Ma'am, the level
around 22182 was the level from where the market made
a tremendous comeback.  There was a good surge.
So tell me once that if we
see where the bottom is seen forming at the level around 22,180, is it the
bottom?  Let's assume the
bottom is formed.  We will not retest that level now.
A retest will not be done before 25,500.
Once such a time will come where we will actually close at 25,
right now we are 243 200 24 250 right round
figure 24230,
then I think once we reach around 25500,
you can keep a little plus minus and
take that much provision.  But there is that much probability.
After that, if things get worse, a
new low may be formed.  Probability it is
linked with further intensification of this
if this war intensifies with war.
If the war is being intensified then this
bottom will come.  Otherwise consider it as a short
bottom.  This is what it means.  You can take this for granted
because everything else in the market
is pricing.  Everything is discounted.  The
market is afraid of only one thing right now.
The new event will happen if
this situation converts into a world war, then only
we will
come.  Otherwise no, it will not come.
Let's see one thing, Ma'am has
given a solution or a remedy here
that brother Anales and Antil, this can happen
only if the conditions of World War arise.
Otherwise, in a way, the
levels here are less likely to be tested.
Tell me 25500 means ma'am the price
is almost above 200 DMA i.e. the price is 25165 which will
go above 200 DMA, it has to go above it
once.  And
if everything comes in place positively.
Watch
It's All About Sentiment at Mary's.   The
Market Is Not Looking at What Good is Going to
Happen.  What's the worst coming market, I
just want to see something positive
here.  This escalation, that is, this
ongoing round of talks, is a positive
thing.  Meaning, what could have been a hit today, it got passed
on and it is always said, this is
valid everywhere that time brings a solution for everything.
So if you're getting the time,
That Means Something might be it.  There is a
hope of Ray of Hope.  Sorry, there is a ray of hope
in the market and that is an important
trigger point.  Apart from this,
we have already said that the fiscal deficit will increase due to weak earnings, growth in selective sectors and a huge dent in some sectors.
Trade deficit will also increase and margins of companies will
increase or decrease.  Inflation will increase,
currency is like on to melt ahead.  Bond
yields are back to us, all these things are in
place.  Everyone knows that this will happen because
what has already happened has an impact.  He has
already taken the price in.  The only thing which is
left is that this war should
proceed slowly, the market has no problem with it.
Some meaning, but if it intensifies and
reaches nuclear level then only there is a
concern or if countries like Russia or China
or India get involved in it.
I have already specifically mentioned the names of three countries
today.  Actually, I was
avoiding it but
if there is direct involvement of India, China and Russia then we can see something worse
in the
market which is also only up to Rs 20,000.   This can happen only if there are
no more verses than this.
Otherwise slow.   Let us
assume that this investment should be
up to 70% for you, save 30% only so that you
can either pyramid the profit in a rising market or if it
falls to 20,000 somewhere then average it there.  That's it, you should get
invested and on Monday we were connected
last time, right
ji,
and from there till now,
whatever targets were discussed for Nifty and Bank Nifty during Monday, were
for the upside only
and both of them were hit, 56000
was talked about for Bank Nifty and for Nifty it was said
that it will come at least around 24300 200, just that is
fine, so here Ma'am has
explained the situation very well and see,
if you take the data of the last war and
see, even in the 10 wars that have happened, if
you look here as per our markets, then
six to seven times
we have lost maximum 8 to 9% only.
Not much more has broken than that.  Ma'am,
let us talk about the back side, brother, now the
situation at the bottom has been created.  These
levels will be retested only when something
unexpected and ultimately something big happens.
But now, the situation that you mentioned about 25500, till
when will it be visible, ma'am?
Ah, not this week.  This week, that is,
this week, I have considered this week closed.
Meaning today is Thursday, tomorrow is Friday,
not in this week.  In the next week, that is,
in this monthly closing, I should see that in this monthly
closing, I am expecting the April series to be
around 25500, not the absolute number, it may be
around 25500, it may be 100 points
higher, it may be 100 points or 150
points lower, but I am expecting
that this April series is going to touch the
price of around 25500 and this is possible, that is, if
you just see that whatever is happening, it should be happening
gradually, whatever talks are going on regarding these war conditions, it should be
slowing down gradually,
but
because gradually you should notice one thing, no doubt
everyone's dependence on crude
is very high, but countries and economies and policy
makers and whatever you want to call it,
corporates are being ready,
people are making solutions for it gradually, so that means, due to the
focus on renewable energy, we are
not going into details, but people are gradually finding its solution, that is, through
policies.  People are getting it made through emphasis,
so preparations are being made.
You should understand that even if things go bad, then there is a
talk of absorbing it, like creating a cushion,
that cushion in the background is being
created, so that it means it is going to be a relief for the people.
Now
whatever it is, this is what the market is about,
but yes, there is no need to be that scared because if you keep on being
scared, nothing will get done.  This is the
market, it's a business.  If you take risks, you will
make money.
Absolutely ma'am.  And we should learn this thing
from mutual funds also.  The way
they invested money in small caps in the month of March
and invested money in a big way, a
lot of things are visible here
and meanwhile, more than 1100 viewers are connected with us.
Many thanks to all the viewers here
who join us early in the morning and
give their time.  Ma'am a spectator yes ma'am
please.
I want to share two stocks with you.
It's time allow.  So as soon as the market
opens, I think that if I
forget later then it will be left behind or it will be
late.  So one is IRB.  There was discussion yesterday also
regarding this, however, IRB
is still in the buying range today.
We can buy it in the range of 21 and 22
for investment.  Right?  And the possible
stop loss is that for now we are
keeping a stop loss of ₹1.5 here.  And as soon as it
crosses above 23 in intraday,
bring the stop loss to 20.  But 20 is
not your target.  Your target is ₹24.  The
first target is ₹24.  The second target is ₹25.5 and the
third target is ₹28.  And I am telling you about the
target till May.  So
a good upside movement can be made in IRB at low
risk.  Then is a fact.  This fact
is also true.
Which second did you mention, ma'am?
Fact Fertilizer.
Good fertilizer ok.
Fact Efficacy Fact.
Ok.
Ok.  So the fact is currently running near 866.
Anyways if you are getting opportunity
in the range of 840 to 870 it is
fine.  So by considering the buying range here, the
first target will probably be 950.  The
second target will
be 1330.  And my third target suggestion is to
wait for around 10150.  And this
is also a favourable risk reward.  Because the
risk you are taking here right now is 740.
And as soon as 950 is gone, you either
book it.  If you want a short term one
day trade, but if you are
doing short term trade, that is, you are looking for proper swing
trading trade, short term trade
opportunity, then you can train at
800 and wait for 900 and 1150.
Ok?  So
sorry 1000 and 1150.
Ok?  That means the first pick
of ma'am is IRB IRB Infra, so the
levels mentioned by ma'am here are 21 to 22
for buying and a stop loss of 20 is being placed.   The
levels of 24, 25, 28 can be seen.  It may be seen
going up to ₹8.
You will have to wait till the month of May.
Apart from that, the fact is that
Fertilizer and Chemicals Travan Core,
here the prices ranging from 950 to 1050 can be
seen here.  So
ma'am, we say that whenever you come, you bring good news
for the investors in the form
of two stocks, as always, like every time, so
this is a very good thing here.
Apart from this, I will take a question from many more viewers,
ma'am.  Then I
start discussing stock specifics with you because there are a
lot of stocks here.  Let us take the question of Deepak ji
or once again Ramchandra Sethi ji
here.  Let's take both of these,
ma'am.  Deepak ji's house is on top of Indus Tower.  They are
asking whether I should exit or
book the loss.  Ramchandra Sethi ji is
saying that the buying done by him in Brain B Solution is at the
price of Rs 225.
Please suggest a little about the stop loss and what will be the target.
Not 280 or 300 ma'am, the price of brainless solution is 200-225.  The
Brain Beast Solution that
he bought, yes first cry ma'am.
So right now let's go to 245, the close is above at 247
and this is the same range where the recommendation was given, they have
held in break piece AU also, it is fine, there is no problem,
right now you should wait for the target of 280 and 345,
now from here you must understand like this that
40, 280 is like, it may take you a week or two
weeks, but 345 is something that you are going to hold
for another two to three months, the
probability is the
same, but you have to have a provision for that because what
I am telling you is that I am saying it will go up by 40% more than the
current price, so be
prepared for that, if you have to hold for two-three months, then you can
hold, the
rest will come soon, you can say that much
and one ma'am is Indus Tower,
yes, Indus Tower, at what price have they bought,
they have given the information, ma'am they are saying that should I just
hold Indus Tower or exit
and  I am in loss
ok I think Indus Tower is coming to 390
390 400 420 20 was the close yesterday
so it can come in that range.  Now, depending on your buying,
you have to decide whether it is a swing trade or an investment.
And when it reaches 390 or 400, it's
bye for me.  I will
look for buying opportunities there.  It Will Be On
My Radar.  It is not that if I get 300 or 400 then
I will immediately get 390 or 400.  There will be a
view of buying initiate immediately.  No we are going to
observe whether the movement is going to continue from here to the upside
or further downside.
So we're going to assess it again at
close to 390 400, but that is absolutely
getting there.
Ok?  So, there is absolute probability that
many reports have come that
due to high capital expenditure, there may be
some impact on earnings pay and free cash flow.
So, ma'am has told many things here,
reflecting them according to the feelings also.
Now let us move ahead.
Here we talk about the results
because a lot will depend on the results.
Market movement also ahead.  Tejas
Network is a Tata company.  Let's
see its results coming, if we look at it on a consolidated basis year after year, then first of all you have the
net profit in front of you.   A
huge decline has been observed.  Here you
can see the net profit.  Earlier the
company was in loss of around Rs 71 crore.  Now it has directly incurred a
loss of Rs 211 crore.  So a big
number is clearly visible which is the loss.  If we
talk about the revenue front, the revenue here has been seen decreasing by 82%
year on year.  If
you look around, earlier it was ₹197 crores, from there it has become ₹333
crores.  Talking about EBITDA, it has
come into negative here.  So all these
things are clearly showing reflection.  The
stock has been beaten down continuously in the recent past.
Ma'am how
should the Trez network be viewed?  What would be your advice
?
Ok.  One is an alarming condition.  In the last one
year, Q&Q has increased by about 1% (less than 1%
but up to 1%) i.e. 0.98% and
retail participation has increased by about 7.5% in one year.   So I
appreciate you all that
you believe in your trades and you hold on
but it has been falling for the last one year.
So there is no need to work anyway
because you must have understood what I mean, in
one year it has declined by like 47%
on the price chart also.
Despite that, people have said in a year, that is, I have
said quarterly because the
position has changed by 1% in the last quarter and
before that it will change by 6%.  This means last
3 months before that till 9 months after that,
why have I said that people
hold the falling stock.  Ok?  Actually, it should
not be done after stop loss.  But
this is a condition.
I am giving you one reference point that in a stock which
showed a 47% decline in the last year,
retail participation has increased by more than 7%.
That means holdings have increased.  I mean that
means they are holding their positions.
So we are assuming
that there is a lot of retail here.
Right?  So because data says that.  And
why is that?  Because the stock has fallen in the last year,
they did not cut the position.  And once
upon a time it was like a stock of 1200 and
today when we are discussing this stock again,
not again I mean we have already discussed it
but when we are discussing it today on 16th April, it is
around 450.  So the only thing to learn
here is that if you do
not cut stop loss then no one
knows whether the stock worth Rs 1000 will become Rs 10 or the stock
worth Rs 10 will become Rs 1000.  So try this, you should have a
stop somewhere.  Put it somewhere.  That's all I had to
explain.  These
reference points will be understood by the rest of the people who understand.  As far as
Tejas Network was concerned,
in our most recent activity
in the last month and on AU also I think the
recommendation came in between around 400, around
350, we had boat this stock
close to 350 last month and from there the
upside movement continued well
and it is going to further that upside
movement, it is likely that the upside
movement is going to continue further.  So
those who are holding it.  What I
said about retail being so big is
because those who are holding it, whether you have been holding
it for a year or for 6 months
or you
bought it at 350 etc. on our recommendation,
whatever the case could be, you should now
hold it here for the
targets of 75, 570 or pardon 570, that is, there will
be a big gap between 570 and 650, the
second target is 650 and it can go up to 800.  So this
is the possibility.  These are the
possibilities that will hit me.  Now
you have to see whether your pricing in this stock is at what level
you are already
buying.  If your weightage in the stock is
not very high.  There is a limited exposure.
If you are comfortable with it and your
financial advisor suggests.  So you
can also go by adding here.  This is because it is
old buying.  I understand.
This is a solution.  If you
want to look into it, then you can get a profitable
exit.  And this is why I am
suggesting it.  Because I feel that
Tejas network is still strong.
You cannot do this in every stock.  So you
can say bye to this.  And whatever position you have, it will be
your old one, if you are not too overweight in it then you
can enter and leave.  For
the targets of 550 650 ground figure
is 630 so that is 7 and 8.  In this way you can chew them.
Or let's say it seems like going from 550
to 800.
Ok?  So here Clarity has come on Tejas Network from Ma'am's side
and here one of
our Prime members is Sudhar Sudarshan ji.
Sudha Shankar ji is saying good morning
Harsh Ambala ma'am.  Ma'am, on top of Crumton Grief,
he has
bought 320 shares at the level of 650.  I have taken 650 shares.
What to do at the price of 320?  Please suggest.
One second
how much wait yes please take your time ma'am
please take your time so he has bought
650 shares at the price of 320
and how many shares he has
bought 600 50 shares 650 shares
at the price of 320 ma'am
alright so will you be able to adjust some
quantity addition you can do if yes ah
mary's me crment grave still by the way
Harsh ji it has come to 33520 already it is with
our members on our darpar.
And it is an hour recommendation and the target for me
from here is a disclosure.  The
first target for me from here is 270.  It is of Rs 310.  And
then I am looking for something a little bigger in this,
350.  So if you are convinced with
this view whose query is this.  So if you want,
you can add as close to 240 250
range.  And today it is most likely going to open in this range.
Today in the market you will get
better buying in some stocks considering today's
market.  And for now,
place your stop loss at 220.
If you do not want to do any addition.  Anyways down the
line six months your exit price with some
profit because it is going up to 350, so
you are also going to get some profit.  So if you
feel that you do not want to increase the risk or
cannot increase it in both the cases, then you can
leave it like this.  I have to come anyway.  But if you
feel that you should get an early exit in 3 months,
then you can add two if you want.
To me it's a it's a
bullish counter.  It's going uphill from here.
End targets have already been discussed.
The price ranges from 270, 310 to 350
and the edge of now target is 220.  As soon as we
reach our first target, we will
shift it to 250.
Ok.  Now let's talk about HDB financials.
This also had results.  But first let me give the
audience some information.  The
stock already ran up a lot yesterday.  There was a rise of 4 to 5%
in the shares of this company.  This is a
subsidiary financial company of HDFC.  Here
you have the net profit.
This shows a jump of about 41%.  If you talk about NII,
here it is 21%.  If you
talk about net interest margin, here
also a better situation is visible.  It has
increased from 0.076% to 0.082% here.
Talking about AUM, there is a jump of 11% in AUM here
which looks quite positive.
Talking about total income, there is a jump of 17% there too.
Ma'am, the
stock has been washed away in the recent past.   It
underperformed here but there was
a good rally in yesterday's markets,
what is the price factor in this company, should we
look at it as per the results or not, there will be an opportunity today also, there will be an
opportunity today also but there is a
need to have a cautious approach, that is only
because the stock has already run, the stock is week
ahead, I am not saying that the results are bad,
I am saying that
right now the stock has
run about 12 to 15% in a few days, since two weeks we can
say like this.  Let's talk about closing April.  There has been an
upside of around 12 to 15% in April.  So, to balance the risk
reward, when the market opens today
and anyway you are getting a 1-2%
discount or let's say
to be specific that if you
get it around 640 then you can buy with 50%
exposure in which the stop loss has to be
kept small for now at 590 for chasing the
targets of like 680 and 730.  This
is the minimum.  One thing that can definitely be done in this is that
as soon as possible, that is, find opportunities for profit pyramiding in it.
So as soon as you
feel that it is going above 650, you
can add further and reduce your stop loss
to 610.  So this strategy can be
used in this.  The counter is not week.
Bye Undip will work in this.
Ok?  Buy on dip will work.  Okay ma'am,
Wipro results are going to be out today ma'am.  And there were a
lot of
investors waiting to see what Wipro's results would be.
Now we will keep an eye on those results.
But if we look at the results of TCS, they were
not very special.
However, the decline was not as much as the street had expected.
Well, I won the deal here too.
If we look at this, which is around 12 billion, the
business that was seen growing due to AI
also came to around $2.3 billion.
Whereas in the previous quarter it was
around 1.8 billion.  This means that the
company is moving ahead in AI in terms of its implementation.
But
how are you looking at Wipro?  What equations are being
formed here, ma'am?   You should say
goodbye to Wipro and sit down.  That
is what the price is saying.  If you try
buying, there is risk everywhere.  Right?  And
if you get the same risk and reward
in the large cap industry then there is nothing like that.
If you are going to take the same risk in small cap or mid
cap or
in emerging industry, then that
risk is a little higher probability wise.
But in a stable company, in a
stable industry, from a stable
brand, all these things coming together in one year are
positive.  So having said this, this
is explained only because
today when you assume that
you are buying Wipro in the range of 200 to 210.
We probably had the same conversation on Monday also.  And we are in the same range, even today the
target has not come.  So if you take this range as
a buying consideration and
you are buying just 80%, 80% that means what
you have decided for a stock, if you are
feeling scared then buy at 80% for the stock which you have
decided,
remaining in the range of 200 to 210,
complete your quantity either above 225
or if it comes a little bit to 190 or 95 then
complete it there.  Because your
stop loss as of now is 175.
Please listen carefully.  Your current stop
loss is 175.  But your target expectation should not be less than
at 240.  Meaning,
his target is to score 240.  So even at 240, if
your profit is pyramiding after 225, then
you will be, then also
you will be in a good profit.  And
by chance, if you get a little bit of gain
from any region, sometimes up to 195,
and there you are trying to improve the price, the
average price is 205,
then also your risk reward will be good.
So Wipro can be considered for a minimum target of Rs 240 and a
maximum target of like Rs 2670.
Good
stock.  The time is also right.  Decide the exposure as per your convenience.  You
can take a lot of risks.  Meaning there is risk in every recommendation.
Understand this.  But if you feel that you need to
manage a little, then wisely invest 80% and
leave the rest for profit pyramiding
or a little bit for averaging, but it will do, I
can say this much,
okay, it will do. We have got clarity from Ma'am
regarding Wipro because today
is its results and we will keep an eye on
it completely, we will tell you what kind
of results have come here Ma'am, there is another company
ICIC LBD, see its results coming
today, the stock will be seen reacting
on the basis of the results, if you look here
in quarter 4, then if we talk about profit,
a decent jump of 7% is seen.  Here it
increased from Rs 510 crore to around Rs 547 crore.
Talking about net premium, there
is a jump of around 10% in net premium
here also.  If you talk about gross return
premium here, there is a jump of around 17% here also.
Apart from this, ma'am, there are two-three
more things.  The gross direct
premium income here has increased by 18%.  This
means that you should understand that the
growth of the industry here is 10% and its growth is
18%.  That means you have beaten
here and beaten by a good margin.
What's the second thing here, ma'am?
Another thing that investors should look at and understand clearly is the balance sheet.   The
solvency ratio here
is above 2.67x.  Whereas the regulatory requirement is
around 1.50x, here
around 1.5x and this is
actually around 2.67x.  That means clearly the
balance sheet here is strong.
Ma'am, how should I read and understand the results
and should I include them in my portfolio
or not?
Should be removed.  And with all this.
So this is called the value investment.   Even
when you're better than the sector, your
numbers are good, you're doing better from the back,
and your margins are your edge.
Your margins are good.  Despite that,
if you are cheaper than the sector, that's something called I
love, yes it is okay, if you
invest money here then it does not sink very easily.
Chances of drowning are everywhere.  But
when you are putting your money in true cases then
you have a little higher chances of
rewards.  And the same combination is
currently being made in ICICI GI.  Now
what should you do in the past today?  First,
understand that this 10 has only risen 10% in the last few days.  The
round figure is 10% mercury, however the
round figure has only gone up 10%.  Flats
open today or even by 1850 if you
get a buying.  Like this you can take that if
you get it in the range of 1800 to 1850 then
buy it quietly.  Buy it and let it work for a few days.  Because we can trust his
performance that he will move ahead in the future.   That's what I am
talking about, right now
I think the range for buying is between Rs 1800 to Rs 1850.
You should definitely consider buying one.  I have
used the exact word.
Ask your financial advisor for the rest.
I think this is a very accurate counter.
And specifically in the insurance sector I got to
touch two points.  I will tell you
about this, something is changing in the market,
so for now
I want to give two targets of 2100 and 2350,
which are big targets, for which we are taking risk, for this
we are
chasing the reward possibilities here at least
25% including the first and second targets
and the risk we are taking is
only 7% here right now.
So you can get a risk reward ratio of more than 1:3 here.
How much time will it take in the end
?  Not more than six months is how long it's going to take.
So it's a good thing.  If you
want, you can take it
to your portfolio.
And yes, what I was saying is that there are some positive
points in the market, that is,
we have seen that the
deposits in banks like CASA etc. have reduced.  Right?
But the good thing is insurance premiums have
increased.  The number of insurances people have also increased due to their insurance price
inflation.
People are investing their money in AUMs and new small
investments are coming into AUMs.  That means the
head count is increasing.  That shows that
gradually investing in our market in fine
financial security is not a taboo anymore.
Or else it is no longer a thing for adults.  This is the
necessity thing
which people have understood or are understanding.
Now you can also understand that my
children or your children will
definitely have insurance policies
etc.  But you and I are also
trying, that is, considering our age, we are also
trying that if possible, we should
take insurance for our parents also.   If
possible, we should make some investment in someone's name.
These things are
happening.  So this change
in the market is a good thing for our market
and this is the reason that despite all this happening,
we have not fallen much.
Okay, so Clarity Ma'am has given this very well.
Ma'am, I would like a small answer and
then we will wind up our show.  Riya
ji owns IDFC First Bank.  He has
purchased at the price of Rs 68.  He has ₹557 shares.
Want to know what to do.
How much is their buying?
Ma'am for ₹68.
All right.  So see you don't have any other option instead of holding it,
you should
hold it and don't look at it again and again, right now I
can only say that if you
look at it again and again you will get panicky, panicky
means you will get scared, so hold it comfortably, in
six-seven months when your overall market
reaches a new high, this stock of yours is
going towards 9095, so you should leave it, there is
no need to track it again and again, it has already
corrected well
and I think there is no more fall left than this.  If there is anything
left, it is very percentage
wide limited.  So just avoid all this
panic because if you see it you will
not be able to control yourself.  That's what I'm just
trying to make you understand.  Going from 90 to 95.
Have some patience, maybe a year or six months may
come soon but hold on and move on.   Don't
look again and again.  That's what I am
suggesting.
Okay ma'am.  So, there is a lot of advice from your side
here, especially on the two IRBs, on the
infra and
also on the Fertilizer and Chemical Shravan Core, that advice has come out here, the
pic that Ma'am has given here and in it the
targets and levels have also been mentioned.  If you
want, you can rewind and watch it as a viewer.
Ma'am recommends shopping here.
Okay ma'am thank you so much and ma'am
please share the disclaimer also.
Yes sir, yes thank you.  Even today, I do not have any
investment stocks in my personal portfolio, which we have recommended.
Members may have them in the equity channel
or in small case portfolios.
Stock recommendations on different media may have been in the past, given
that common stocks remain.  So there are
the ma'am
one more thing I would like to stop you.  One of
our viewers is JM Baberujis over.
Because his question has been repeated many times
here.  So it is in loss of 9%.
Almost their buying is at ₹168 and they are
asking what should be done?
GM Bru, I remember I had recommended three days ago that if the
target is not reached and the
stop loss is also not reached then hold it
and rest yes,
I have given the stop loss and target and till
now neither of them has been hit.  So hold it with that
further disclosure again that I do
not have any of the stocks in my portfolio that I have recommended to you guys here.
Trading and investment are subject to
market risk, work accordingly.
A SEBI license or registration
certificate by SEBI by NSM gives no way
of guarantee that the property will be.  And past
performance does
not guarantee future profits, nor does it give any indication.
It's not a reference to future
performance.  So all that, the
biggest thing before leaving is
that risk management is the key and
money cannot be made without taking risks.  So this
is something like that.  We have to cross the river of fire.  So you will have to learn to
manage it.
Thank you so much.
Yes, learn to love with passion.
An advice is being given by ma'am.  Thank you
so much ma'am.  Thank you very much for joining us.
Hello.
So this was the overall show and which
shows are going to be coming up a lot throughout the day.
So let us know about it.
Talk about 10:00 in the morning.  Anshul Jain ji
will join.  VL Ambala ji will join.  Amit
Jain ji will join here.  You will
see friends joining in the market.  If we talk about 1:00 pm,
Pradeep Hadar will be seen joining
here.  Apart from this, if you watch at 4:00 pm, there will be a
special show related to mutual funds
and at 9:00 pm, do
not forget to know every update related to crypto in Crypto Counter.  So please excuse
me for now.  Thank you very much.
Mutual fund investments are subject to
market risk